原創翻譯  雙語字幕
最新連載海外影視劇下載
請登陸 www.YYeTs.com
僅供交流學習  禁止商用盈利
翻譯     有仇必報賽太公  獨醉  油膩希   貓中之王
校對     超能力是貧窮賽
后期      灰灰是菇涼      時間軸    加森
總監     新浪微博@賽太公
生
活
大
爆
炸
第十二季  第四集
你在干嘛呢
Hey, whatcha doing?
把我們的結婚照修更好
Improving our wedding photos.
那挺好
Oh, that's nice.
等等  修完我還在里面吧
Wait, I'm still in them, right?
當然啦   不只是你還在
Of course. And not only you.
我還加進了幾個不克前來的賓客
I've added some guests who couldn't be there.
在我爸爸旁邊的是誰啊
Who's that next to my father?
萊特兄弟[發明飛機]
The Wright brothers.
他們為什么來了我們婚禮
And why are they at our wedding?
弟弟奧維爾·萊特是因為我崇拜他
Orville, because I admire him;
哥哥威爾伯·萊特則是弟弟帶來的伴
Wilbur, because he was Orville's plus-one.
你收到了一個叫丹的人給你寄的電郵
You got an e-mail from someone named Tam.
丹嗎  他找我想干嘛
Tam? What does he want?
他好像要帶他兒子來參觀加州理工
looks like he's coming to give his son a tour of Caltech.
他希望能跟你敘敘舊
He's hoping you guys can meet up.
他當然希望啦  可不是嗎
He would like that, wouldn't he?
這電郵的重點的確在此
Well, that is the gist of the e-mail.
丹是誰啊
Who's Tam?
他是我成長階段時最要好的朋友
He was my best friend in the whole world growing up.
真的嗎  那我怎么從來沒聽你提過他
Really? Why have I never heard you mention him before?
我當然有過啊   我肯定光是這周
Oh, of course I have. I'm sure I've mentioned him,
我就起碼提了有5次吧
like, five times this week.
我可不這么認為
I don't think you have.
丹  丹  丹  丹  丹  才周四就已經五次了呢
Tam! Tam! Tam! Tam! Tam! There, it's only Thursday.
我不只是喝到瘋牛奶  我還買回了頭瘋牛
I didn't just drink the crazy milk, I bought the crazy cow.
所以你真的跟這個認識不久的女人訂婚了嗎
So, are you actually engaged to this woman you just met?
是啊
Yeah.
老實招來  是不是她把你肚子搞大了
Tell us the truth. Did she get you pregnant?
呵呵
Very funny.
各位  我很需要你們的幫助
Guys, I need your help, okay?
我想給她買個訂婚戒指
I'm trying to buy her engagement ring.
你覺得這款如何
What do you think of this?
你覺得她會喜歡這款嗎
Do you think she'll like this one?
很難說啊  我對她的認識那么少
Well, it's hard to say, not knowing much about her.
她有手指嗎
Does she have fingers?
有  她有十根手指
Yes, she has ten fingers
以及十根腳趾  應該啦
and ten toes. Probably.
等我看到她穿涼鞋我再告訴你
I'll get back to you after I see her in sandals.
你們知道謝爾頓小時候
Hey, did you guys know that Sheldon had
有一個死黨叫丹嗎
a best friend growing up named Tam?
是那只幻想出來的會說話的考拉嗎
Was that the imaginary talking koala?
不  他是個活人  貌似背叛過他
No. He's a real person who apparently betrayed him.
是啊  那只考拉也背叛過他
Yeah, so did the koala.
我試著問過他
I tried to ask him about it,
但他引用了婚姻協議中的第3節第5條
and he invoked section three, article five of the marriage contract:
"屁事  關你"
beeswax comma none of your.
我也不能窺探他隱私
I can't pry. I mean,
我得尊重他的意愿
I have to respect his wishes.
我真好奇那兄弟是做了什么事
Wow. I wonder what that guy could've done
能讓謝爾頓不跟他說話20年
to make Sheldon not talk to him for 20 years.
不知道我也做一次還能不能有效
I wonder if it'd work a second time.
我在擠母乳
I'm pumping!
我是佩妮
It's Penny.
請進
Oh. Come in.
我以為你在擠母乳呢
I thought you were pumping.
我以為你是我老板
I thought you were my boss.
你聽我說
Okay, listen,
我好擔心拉杰婚姻這件事啊
I'm really worried about this whole Raj thing.
是啊  他這么著急想結婚  也是奇怪了
I know, he's so desperate to get married, which is weird,
我們明明做了這么不好的示范
because I can't imagine we make it look that great.
就是啊
I know, right?
如果這女人以后會加入我們的圈子
You know, if this woman's gonna be around,
我覺得我們應該先去觀察她一下
I think we should check her out a little.
我在網上搜過  她沒有照片分享網的賬號
I looked online. She doesn't have an Instagram,
所以她不是80歲了就是有古怪
which means she's either 80 or something's wrong with her.
我可以讓我爸查查她
Well, I could ask my dad.
或許他可以讓他以前的警察朋友
Maybe he can get some of his old cop buddies
對她做一個背景調查
to do a background check on her.
-他會愿意嗎  -當然啦
- Would he do that? - ‭Of course.
他是個只按自己規矩辦事的退休警察
He's a retired cop who plays by his own rules.
老爸
Hi, Daddy.
沒  我挺好的
No, everything's good.
我只是有個忙想請你幫
I just have a favor to ask.
是這樣的  我的朋友拉杰
Yeah, so, my friend Raj
要娶一個他都不太熟的女人
is marrying this woman that he barely knows,
我想問問你能不能托關系
and I wanted to see if you could use your connections
挖一點她的黑料出來
to dig up any dirt on her.
沒問題
Sure.
好的  愛你
Okay. Love you.
-他愿意嗎  -不行  他不愿意  說是非法的
- Is he in? - Absolutely not. He won't do it. It's totally illegal.
你不是說他只按自己規矩辦事嗎
I thought you said he played by his own rules.
的確  但很不巧  他的規矩跟真實法律很接近
He does, but apparently, they're very similar to the actual rules.
真不敢相信謝爾頓有一個
I still can't believe Sheldon had a best friend
我們從沒聽說過的死黨
we've never heard about.
某人在吃醋
Ooh, somebody's jealous.
我才不吃醋
I'm not jealous.
萊納德  在這里可以放寬心  你允許脆弱
‭Leonard, this is a safe space-- it's okay to be vulnerable.
我的意思只是
All I'm saying is
我連這家伙的如廁時間都了如指掌
you know the timing of a fellow's bowel movements,
怎么會想到他還那么多秘密
you don't think there's a lot left to discover.
真好奇丹到底做了什么
I wonder what Tam could have done.
如果謝爾頓不愿意談
Hmm. Well, if Sheldon doesn't want to talk about it,
那肯定是令他很難過的事情了
it's got to be pretty upsetting.
我有他哥哥小喬治的電話  他可能知道
I have his brother George's number-- he might know.
真的嗎  你有小喬治的電話
Really? You have George's number?
醋缸要滿了
So so jealous.
當然  我記得丹這號人物
Yeah, sure, I remember Tam,
謝爾頓的越南人好朋友
Sheldon's little Vietnam buddy.
他倆從小就一起玩
The two of them were always running around together.
所以發生什么事了
So, what happened?
什么意思
What do you mean?
謝爾頓從來沒提過他
Well, I mean, Sheldon never talks about him.
他們多年不曾聯絡  他也沒來參加婚禮
They haven't spoken in years. He wasn't at the wedding.
他沒來嗎
He wasn't?
好吧  這就尷尬了
All right. Well, this is embarrassing.
因為我跟一位我以為是丹的人聊了可久了
'cause I had a long conversation with someone who I thought was Tam.
等等  所以你不知道他們為什么而吵
Wait, wait, so you don't know what their fight was about?
我也希望我知道答案
I wish I could help you, boys.
不過你們知道嗎
But, you know,
謝爾頓小時候曾經有一個仇敵名單
Sheldon used to keep an enemies list when he was a kid.
他現在還留著呢
Oh, he still does.
真的嗎  我以為那已經和他的如廁時間表
Really? I figured that went the same way
同樣下場了
as his bathroom schedule.
如果你是指電子化  云端化并帶注釋  你答對了
If you mean digitized, annotated and put online, it did.
也許那上面有答案
Maybe that'll tell you something.
你們看的時候  如果名單還有
Hey, while you're looking at it, if I'm still on there
我尿在他洗發水瓶里的那件事...
for peeing in his shampoo bottle...
算了  留在上面吧
Eh, you know what, just leave it.
回見了各位
See ya, boys. Bye.
再見  好了  找到他的仇敵名單了
Bye. ‭All right, got his enemies list.
他更新了他的界面
Ooh, he updated the interface.
可以按姓  名
You can search by first name,
和怨恨的程度分別查找
last name or length of grudge.
丹在上面嗎
Is Tam on it?
找找看哈
Let's see.
找到了  在這里  丹·阮
Yep. Right here. Tam Nguyen.
太好了  他到底做了什么
Oh, great. What did he do?
等等  我得先同意這些服務條款
Hold on. I have to agree to the terms of service.
不  我不是個機器人
No, I'm not a robot.
好了
Okay.
"以下物品哪些是植物"
"Which of these are plants?"
成功了
And we're in.
好的  上面說什么
Great. What-what does it say?
那個
Well...
"他心知肚明自己做了什么"
"He knows what he did."
搞什么呀
Oh, come on.
等等  等等
Wait. Wait, wait, wait,
如果丹知道自己做了什么  我們可以直接問他
if Tam knows what he did, we can just ask him.
他明天要帶兒子來學校參觀呢
He's gonna be on campus tomorrow showing his son around.
這不會讓謝爾頓生氣嗎
Won't that make Sheldon mad?
任何事都能讓謝爾頓生氣
Everything makes Sheldon mad.
看看這名單
Yeah. Look at his list.
吉姆·韓生[芝麻街布偶之父]
Jim Henson for, quote,
"在電視上創造了一個又大又黃又嚇人的鳥
"Putting a terrifying, giant yellow bird on television
引發我噩夢連連"
and in my nightmares."
這里真不錯
Oh, this is so nice. Mm-hmm.
也許除了和安努打招呼之外
Maybe instead of introducing ourselves to Anu,
我們可以訂個房間
we could just get a room,
點些吃的  好好小睡一覺
order some food and take a nap.
我以前上過這種鬼話的當
Yeah, I've fallen for that line before.
最后絕對不是以小睡結束的
It never leads to napping.
那肯定是她了
That must be her.
她真可愛
Oh. She's cute.
我已幫您訂好了《漢密爾頓》音樂劇的兩張票
Okay, I got you two seats to Hamilton tonight.
您可以來服務臺去取票
Your tickets will be at the concierge desk.
不用謝
Of course. My pleasure.
有什么可以幫您的嗎
May I help you?
我是來取《漢密爾頓》音樂劇票的
Yes, I'm here to pick up our Hamilton tickets.
住嘴
Stop.
你好  我們是拉杰的朋友
Hi. We're Raj's friends.
我是佩妮  這位是博納黛特
I'm Penny. This is Bernadette.
我們想來和你打個招呼
We just came by to introduce ourselves.
所以你們是來打探我的嗎
So you came to check me out?
她好聰明  我喜歡
She's smart. I like her.
我們只是想看看能否約你吃晚飯
We just want to see if we could take you to dinner
多了解你一點
and get to know you a bit.
你們人真好  不如今晚下班后吧
That sounds nice. How about tonight after work?
我們可以去巴維爾餐館
Maybe we can go to Bavel.
我也想去呀  可那地方不可能訂到位
Oh, I wish. That place is impossible to get into.
拜托  我的超能力就是進各種不可能的地方
Oh, please. Getting into impossible places is my superpower.
我也是
Me, too.
我可以把自己塞進一個烘干機
I can fit my whole body in our dryer.
安排好了  8點半
All set. 8:30.
太好了  那就今晚見了
Wow. Okay, well, we'll see you tonight.
回見了
See you then. ‭Okay.
拜
Bye.
她什么餐館都能訂到位
She can get into any restaurant,
卻只能找拉杰做她的丈夫嗎
but the best husband she can find is Raj?
不是丹
Not Tam.
找到他了
Got him.
-你是丹·阮嗎  -是我
Tam Nguyen? ‭Yeah. Yes.
我兒子參觀完了嗎
Is my son done with his tour?
我不知道  我們其實是謝爾頓·庫珀的朋友
No idea. We're actually friends of Sheldon Cooper.
我一直嘗試在聯系他呢
Oh, I've been trying to get in touch with him,
但從來沒收到回信  他還好嗎
but I never heard back. Is he okay?
如果你是指生理上  還好
Well, if you mean physically, yes.
如果你是指其他方面  不好
If you mean every other way, no.
-他人在這里嗎  -不在
- So, is he here? - Uh, no.
他沒有來
He-he didn't come.
他有點...
He's, uh...
他還生氣呢
he's still pretty upset about...
你懂的
you know.
我懂什么
I know what?
就是那個呀  你肯定知道的
Come on, you-you must know.
我不知道呀  我們快20年沒講話了
No, we haven't talked in, like, 20 years.
對嘛  就是因為...
Right. Because...
你懂的
you know.
我覺得他不懂呢
I don't think he knows.
你們在說什么呀
What are you guys talking about?
你是為什么和謝爾頓鬧掰的呢
Why did you and Sheldon stop being friends?
-你做了什么  -別擔心
- What did you do? - And don't worry,
雖然我們才剛見面
even though we just met you,
我們覺得你是對的  他肯定錯了
we think you're right and he's wrong.
我什么都沒做呀
I didn't do anything.
他搬去加州  我們就漸行漸遠了
He moved to California, and we just drifted apart.
拜托  中間肯定還有些什么事...
Oh, come on, there's got to be something...
-你們在干什么  -嘿  謝爾頓
- What is going on here? - Oh, hey, Sheldon.
-我們剛見到了...  -謝爾頓  見到你真好
- We just met... - Sheldon! So good to see you!
丹
Tam.
好久不見了
It's been a long time.
并沒有久到讓背叛的傷痛灰飛煙滅
Mm, not long enough to erase the sting of betrayal.
我怎么背叛你了
How did I betray you?
你知道自己做了什么
You know what you did.
我給你劇透一下
Uh, let me catch you up.
他真心不知道
He does not.
當我搬到加州時  你做了什么
When I moved to California, what did you do?
我留在德州了啊
I stayed in Texas.
你們看看這貨
Do you believe this guy?!
所以他是你小時候的死黨嗎
So, he was your best friend growing up?
是的
Yes.
你們德州是沒有其他小朋友了嗎
Were there no other kids in Texas?
你這人到底怎么回事
Hey. What is going on with you?
我不想聊這件事
I don't want to talk about it.
你一定有一個足夠蠢的理由
Well, I'm sure you have a perfectly stupid reason.
我才不會為了蠢理由做什么事
I don't do anything for a stupid reason.
除了"學海盜說話日"
Except, perhaps, Talk Like a Pirate Day,
但我覺得那是滑稽多過蠢
and I'd argue that's more whimsical than stupid.
我之前想搞清楚丹做錯了什么
You know, I was curious to find out what Tam had done wrong.
結果他根本什么都沒做  而我一點都不意外
Why am I not surprised the answer is nothing?
這么說你站在他那邊了
So you're taking his side.
你個壞血病爛狗
You scurvy dog.
壞血病又稱水手病  主要由缺乏維生素C導致
你給我小心點  我的敵人名單現在有空位了
You watch yourself. There is room on my enemies list
因為食堂的阿姨們終于告訴我
now that the cafeteria ladies finally told me
辣椒醬里放了什么了
what's in the chili.
順便說下  別吃那個辣椒醬
By the way, don't eat the chili.
等一下  其實呢
Wai-Wai-Wait, you know what?
吃吧
Do.
小心點  謝爾頓
Be careful, Sheldon.
你承受不了失去第二個死黨
I don't think you can afford to lose a second best friend.
我可沒看到有人要排隊當你第三個死黨
I don't see anyone lining up to be your third.
等一下
D... Wait.
搜索"回懟金句"
"Snarky comebacks..."
找到了
Oh, here we go.
"你這輩子都是混球
"You have your entire life to be a jerk,
休息一天也無妨吧"
why not take today off?"
這句挺刺耳的  不過是他自找的
That was harsh, but he was asking for it.
這地方太贊了
This place is amazing.
真不敢相信你給我們訂到了位子
I can't believe you got us in here.
這算是我的工作
Well, it's kind of my job.
通常客人會有小費  但我就讓你們自己決定吧
Usually I get tipped for it, but I'll leave that up to you.
快看  那個好像是勒布朗
Look, I think that's LeBron over there.
球星詹姆斯嗎
James?
不然是詹姆斯·路人甲嗎
No, LeBron Kershenbaum.
你們想知道什么
So, what do you want to know?
你看起來是個聰明成功的女性
Well, you seem like a smart, successful woman,
你為什么會想跟一個剛認識的人結婚
why would you want to marry someone you just met?
問得好
Fair question.
我二十幾歲時  試過普通的戀愛方式
In my 20s, I tried this the normal way.
遇到了一個男人  墜入愛河
You know, met a guy, fell in love,
然后我們同居了
we moved in together.
我供他上烹飪學校  編劇課程
I put him through culinary school, screenwriting classes,
最后在他想當助產士時把他甩了
and finally dumped him when he wanted to become a midwife.
然后我意識到
Then I realized,
我父母很幸福  他們就是包辦婚姻
my parents are happy; they had an arranged marriage.
我為什么要抗拒這個
Why am I fighting this?
我也說不好  我為愛而結的婚
I dunno, I married for love
結果也...
and it turned out...
還行
fine.
我的也是
Oh, yeah, me, too.
你好
Hi.
霍華德  今天你走運了
Howard, today is your lucky day.
萊納德出局了  現在你是我新任死黨
Leonard's out, you're my new best friend.
我也不為此感到激動
Well, I'm not thrilled about it either,
不過就這樣了
but here we are.
好吧
Okay, fine.
伯納黛特在嗎
Is Bernadette there?
不在
Sh... No.
只有斯圖爾特
Just Stuart?
我等會再打給你
Let me call you back.
讓我猜猜
Let me guess.
丹的事嚴重性升級
This thing with Tam escalated,
現在你生萊納德的氣了
and now you're mad at Leonard
要找新一任死黨
and looking for a new best friend?
你好了解人家
You know me so well.
可惜你不能當我死黨
It's too bad you can't be my best friend.
我可以啊
I can be.
你不能同時當我的妻子和最好的朋友
You can't be my wife and my best friend.
不然我要跟誰抱怨你的事
Who would I complain about you to?
告訴我發生什么了
Just tell me what happened.
萊納德背著我去找丹聊了  還站在他那邊
Leonard talked to Tam behind my back and took his side.
他可是對我做出過那么過分的事  你能相信嗎
And after what he did to me. Can you believe it?
不能  我很震驚  也很憤怒
No. I'm-I'm shocked and outraged.
現在告訴我  我為什么震驚和憤怒
Now, tell me why I'm shocked and outraged.
好吧
Fine.
當我被加州理工的研究所錄取時
When I got accepted to grad school at Caltech,
我很害怕要搬到離家這么遠的地方
I was afraid to move so far away from home.
于是丹說他會跟我一起搬出來
So Tam said he'd move out here with me
做我的室友
and be my roommate.
然后在暑假期間  他找了個女朋友
Then, over the summer, he got a girlfriend,
即使他已經看完我給他的
even after reading all the pamphlets
那些介紹性病的小冊子
I gave him about social diseases.
我記得你給過我那些小冊子
Aw, I remember when you gave me those pamphlets.
總之  丹陪她留在了德州
Anyway, Tam stayed with her in Texas,
我只能獨自搬來這里
and I had to move out here all by myself.
你當時一定很害怕
That must've been scary.
是的
It was.
我很孤單寂寞
I was lonely, and I thought
心想我再也交不到朋友了
I'd never make a friend again.
有很長一段時間  我確實沒交朋友
And for a long time, I didn't.
但之后你交到了
But then you did.
還是很棒的摯友
And great friends.
你想想  如果當初丹跟你一起搬來
If you think about it, if Tam had moved out here with you,
誰知道你的生活會變成什么樣子
who knows what your life would've been like.
什么事
Yes.
我是萊納德·霍夫斯塔德
Uh, I'm Leonard Hofstadter.
第3季第22集
我在電話里說想租你的公寓 你說...
I called you about the apartment. You said...
叫他滾蛋  你已經有室友了
Tell him to go away. You already have a roommate.
新來的鄰居
New neighbor?
第1季第1集
你們好呀
Oh, hi.
-你好  -你好
- Hi. - ‭Hi.
Hi. ‭Hi.
丹  快看啊
Tam, look.
謝爾頓在擁抱我
Sheldon's hugging me.
第2季第11集
這是農神節的奇跡
It's a Saturnalia miracle.
謝爾頓  出來
Sheldon, come here.
第3季第14集
逗你玩
Bazinga.
不  我的生活還是會很棒
No, my life would've still been great.
客人提過最瘋狂的要求是什么
So what is the craziest request anyone's ever made?
其實我不能說
Oh, you know, I can't really say.
禮賓部和客人之間有保密協議
Concierge-guest confidentiality.
不是吧  真有這回事
Really, that's a thing?
沒有
No.
有一次  我得在凌晨三點到沃爾瑪去
This one time, I had to go to Walmart at 3:00 a.M.
因為歌手小甜甜布蘭妮想吹泡泡
because Britney Spears needed to blow bubbles.
好酷啊
Oh. ‭That is so cool.
對了  千萬別告訴拉杰你見過小甜甜布蘭妮
By the way, do not tell Raj that you met Britney Spears,
因為他會激動到原地去世
because he will literally die.
我們聊了很多我的事了
We've been talking so much about me,
跟我說說拉杰吧
tell me about Raj.
你是想把我們灌醉
Okay, are you trying to get us drunk
讓我們大聊朋友的八卦嗎
so we'll dish on our friend?
效果卓越  你想知道什么
'Cause it's totally gonna work, what do you want to know?
他是什么樣的人
What kind of guy is he?
他是好人
He is great.
非常好的人
So great. ‭
那他為什么還單身
How come he's still single?
-他是好人  -非常好的人  沒錯
- He's great. - ‭So great. Yeah.
少來
Come on.
真的沒什么可說的
There's really nothing to tell.
和拉杰在一起玩非常開心
Raj is so much fun to hang out with.
他像我們的閨蜜
He's like one of our girlfriends.
我這話是褒義
And I mean that in a good way.
但也是貶義
But also a bad way.
還有嗎
Anything else?
-沒了  -沒了
- No. - ‭No.
他和他的狗一起洗澡
I mean, h-he takes baths with his dog,
但并不是以奇怪的方式
but not in a weird way.
也不是正常方式  他們都穿泳衣
Or a normal way; they both wear swimsuits.
每次休·杰克曼唱歌他都會哭
He also cries every time Hugh Jackman sings.
不是梨花帶雨嬌美狀  而是一把鼻涕一把淚
But not cute sniffles-- full-on snot sobs.
但他真的很好
But he is great.
-太好了  -沒錯
- So great. - ‭Yeah.
你好  謝爾頓
Hello, Sheldon.
你好  丹  感謝你來
Hello Tam. Thank you for coming.
我只想讓你知道
I just want you to know that, um...
我原諒你
I forgive you.
我什么都沒做
I didn't do anything.
但我依然愿意
And yet, here I am,
做大度的那個人
still being the bigger man.
聽著  我當時愛著貝絲
Look, I was in love with Beth,
她令我開心
and she made me happy.
是嗎
Y... Really?
她讓你玩她的火車模型嗎
Did she let you play with her train set?
可以說她讓我"玩她的"
In a manner of speaking.
謝爾頓  我需要留在德州
Sheldon, I needed to stay in Texas.
你需要來這里
And you needed to come here.
我知道你會有出色的成績
I knew you were gonna do amazing things,
會認識尊敬你的出色的人
and meet amazing people who were gonna respect you,
因為你才華橫溢
because you're brilliant.
也因為他們永遠不必從大垃圾箱中把你撈出來
And because they never had to fish you out of a dumpster.
還是撈過的  那時候
Well, they have, but it was during
我短暫地迷上了跑酷
my short-lived parkour phase.
我不是有心讓你生氣
I didn't mean to upset you.
我想讓你知道  對于你的成績
And I want you to know I'm really proud
我非常驕傲
of everything you've done.
謝謝你
Thank you.
我的日子的確過得不錯
It did work out for me.
很遺憾你的日子過得不好
And I'm sorry that things didn't work out for you.
我也過得很好啊
They did work out for me.
丹  你不必因為我偽裝堅強
Oh, Tam, you don't need to be brave on my account.
我沒有
I'm not.
我有出色的妻子和孩子
I have a great wife and amazing children.
我非常快樂
I'm very happy.
堅強  堅強的丹
Brave, brave Tam.
似乎佩妮和伯納黛特昨晚玩得很開心
Sounds like Penny and Bernadette had fun last night.
我知道
I know.
妮妮回家時很醉了
Bernie came home pretty drunk.
她還想睡在烘干機里
She tried to sleep in the dryer.
你們都認識丹  我在高中時的死黨
Hello, you all remember Tam, my best friend from high school.
-當然  -你好嗎
- Yeah. ‭Of course. ‭- How's it going?
謝爾頓帶我和我兒子到處參觀
Sheldon's been showing me and my son around.
現在我們知道了所有干凈的衛生間在哪里
Now we know where all the clean bathrooms are. ‭
你要善用記憶法
You just remember the mnemonic:
小號小號  圖書館讓你笑
if it's number one, the library's fun,
大號大號  地下室剛剛好
if it's number two, the basement's for you.
我很高興你們和好了
I'm glad you guys made up.
我意識到我的生活很幸福
Well, I realized my life turned out great,
記仇太傻了
and it's silly to hold a grudge.
我根本不知道我們吵架了  所以和好很容易
And I had no idea we were fighting, so it was easy.
別擔心  萊納德
Uh, don't worry, Leonard,
你依然是我的加州死黨
you're still my California best friend.
酷
Cool.
你現在想做什么
So, what do you want to do now?
去火車玩具商店  還是漫畫書店
Go to the train store, go to the comic book store?
其實我要帶兒子去機場了
Actually, I have to grab my son and head to the airport.
我正準備叫出租車
I was just about to call a cab.
別傻了  你不用叫出租車
Don't be silly, you don't have to call a cab.
你是我交情最老的朋友
You're my oldest friend.
萊納德會送你的  對嗎  萊納德
Leonard will take you. Right, Leonard?
當然
Sure.
可以走了嗎
Shall we?
慢著慢著
Eh, eh, eh, hold on.
我20年沒見丹了
I haven't seen Tam in 20 years,
給我一個機會道別
give me a chance to say good-bye.
拜
Bye.
你看
Check it out--
勒布朗·詹姆斯在網上發了我和他的合影
LeBron James posted a picture of me and him on Instagram.
我沒看到你
I don't see you.
在他后面
Look right behind him.
沒看到
No.
你看到他左肩后的桌子嗎
Okay. You see that table just past his left shoulder?
再過去兩桌  看右邊
Now go back two more tables and over to the right.
我只看到一塊黃斑
All I see is a yellow smudge.
那是我
That's me!
是拉杰
Oh, it's Raj.
拉杰  我和佩妮在一起
Hey Raj, I'm here with Penny.
你們對安努亂說了些什么
What the hell did you two say to Anu?
你這話是什么意思呢
Whatever do you mean?
你們為什么告訴她
Why, why would you tell her
我用女士體香劑
I wear ladies' deodorant?
因為你是男人  很好玩啊
Uh, because you're a boy and it's really funny.
好吧  請原諒我
Oh, oh, okay. Pardon me
能有身上帶雛菊飄香的自信
for having the confidence to smell daisy-fresh.
幫我個忙  離她遠一點
Just do me a favor and stay away from her.
老天  現在我覺得好內疚
Ugh, God, now I feel bad.
是啊
I know.
也許我們應該再和她出去
Maybe we should take her out again
說些拉杰的好話
and do some damage control.
這是個好主意
You know, that's a good idea.
你覺得她能把我們搞進蘇荷館嗎
Think she can get us into SoHo House?
不知道  但我們欠拉杰人情  必須試試
I don't know, but we owe it to Raj to try.